[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[Sigh of temperature]
- (Gion) Is EM worth it?
- (Intern) Nop
(Gion) Was the last turn OS?
How about there?
(Intern) Not even there
I'm so scared of second year teachers
(Gion) The problem is that the OS is two years apart.
For OBGY, the 1 year gap is a problem.
(Intern) Why? What is it like?
Everyone
It hurts a little
[Interesting music]
[Mother 1’s heavy breathing]
(Democratic Party) Breathe
(Temperature) One person's BT is too low
It's 100% hypothermia.
(Lee Young) Please give strength to the mother.
[Mother 1’s heavy breathing]
Ha, I think I'm going to die
There's still a long way to go, please give me strength
(Intern) If it’s hypothermia
The room temperature in the labor room
- Shouldn’t it be uploaded?
- (Lee Young) That’s right
- (Temperature) No.
- (Lee Young) Please give me strength one more time
(temperature) the other one
Come on, mother!
- (Temperature) High fever
- (Jaeil) Breathe in
[Mother 2’s labored breathing]
Oh! Okay, okay, okay.
One, two, three!
Breathe!
[Mother 2’s screams]
[Mother 2’s heavy breathing]
one more time
One, two, three!
Breathe!
[Mother 2’s screams]
[Mother 2’s powerful scream]
[Jaeil’s strength-giving elasticity]
Mother, please give me strength.
[Mother 3’s strength-giving elasticity]
(Temperature) Another person’s BP is too high
high blood pressure
one more time
[Mother 3’s strength-giving elasticity]
Wow, good job! It was great!
- Oh, I love it, I love it!
- (temperature) the other one
All of that is immeasurable
No diagnosis
Teacher, I'm so sick.
[Mother 4’s pained moans]
(Jiyoung) The mother will breathe.
[Mother 4’s screams]
Mother, are you singing before your eyes?
[breathing heavily] No.
Well it's still far away
When the front turns yellow, call me then.
[Tickling sound effect]
(Gion) Turned out to be not human
What are you saying?
[Mother 4’s screams]
(Intern) [Distressed] Me next month
It was my turn at the obstetrics and gynecology department, but I failed.
But again
In some ways
I think it's okay
Oh, what are you saying it hurts?
(Temperature) The above annual difference is strange.
Seeing a baby being born
I really like it
Both the mother and the patients are friendly.
It's hard
ok
[Mobile phone warning alarm sound]
- Oh, what a surprise!
- (Intern) I’m surprised.
Oh, really
Since you're talking nonsense, the alarm sounds right away.
[Intern's light laughter]
medicine alarm
I also have high blood pressure, so it’s time to take medicine.
let's go
(Intern) Let’s go
[lively music]
(Jaehwi) They’re interns, right?
So, will you be a fellow?
(Jaehwi) Uh, yes, that’s right
(Jeongmin) Intern Tak Gion
Don’t you think you’re interested in obstetrics and gynecology?
Are you already preparing to recruit interns?
What, it's already July, it's late
This was the first year of farming, and it wasn't great.
If the harvest is poor next year, we will all be ruined.
Get your mind straight
(Jaehwi) Oh
yes
(Jeongmin) Let’s go
(Jaehwi) Yes
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
'Life as a Major' theme song]
[lively music]
[Makes a yuck sound]
I can't figure it out
I got scolded by Professor Seo Jeong-min so much.
(Jaeil) I saw what you were doing and asked me to practice.
- Nam Kyung-ah
- (Namkyung) Huh?
- I heard you got scolded too?
- no?
I'm not scolded, am I?
(Nankyung) I just heard some nagging.
[Lee Young sighs]
He always pretended to do things half-heartedly
You must have practiced a lot?
(Lee Young) You didn’t?
(Japanese) When performing abdomen pasha sucheo
Professor Gong Gong-seon
They told me to sew it tightly to avoid honeycomb.
Professor Seo Jeong-min said that if you sew too tightly,
They say something because it doesn't flow through the organization.
Oh, you don't know the difference between the two?
What he did now is Seo Jeong-min
(Lee Young) Oh, really?
(Sabi) Didn’t you know?
(Lee Young) Yeah, I just go from time to time
Did you do what you were told?
Wow, is this guy a genius?
What is genius
They say that if your brain is bad, your hands will suffer.
(Nanjing) My hands were having a hard time
I guess I got caught by chance, whatever.
(Jaeil) Lee Young is smart
I heard you were always first in high school?
I'm number 1 in my grades
He came in first place on the mock exam.
We were rivals for three years?
(Lee Young) There’s no need for all that.
What do you do if you get first place in high school?
Now I have no money and I'm hungry
I'm a complete beggar
But did you buy it again?
(Nankyung) This?
12 months interest-free installments
This color is in stores nationwide
I heard there is only one left, what should I do?
I should buy it
Pretty, right?
Well, not my style
It's not even mom's bag
I don't know what's trending
Don’t you know the old money look?
Do you have somewhere to take it?
(Nanjing) Why isn’t it there?
Coming to work, leaving work
Out of the hospital, go home
(Japan) There are many places to go in Namgyeong.
I go on dates and meet my boyfriend.
How many times do I tell you that we broke up
When did you say it was just a fight again?
(Japan) I'm going
[Sound of door opening and closing]
(Nankyung) We broke up, it’s over!
Even if I call you again, I will never answer.
Even if I cry and pray and say we should meet
I can't do it
Because we'll never meet, Chi.
(Sabi) That sound again
Did they fight or break up?
When it's all sorted out, just tell me the conclusion.
(Nankyung) It’s all sorted out, is it all sorted out?
[Sound of door opening and closing]
Oh, it's really sorted out.
[Mobile phone call incoming sound]
(Gion) Teacher
Emergency room patient results are out
(Namkyung) Ki Dong-ah, call me when you get angry.
I'll wait
It's an emergency room.
[Nanjing’s light sigh]
I'm going
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[Sparkling and tempting sound effect]
[Calm music]
(Japan) Cell phone...
[Jaeil's urgent groan]
[Sound of door closing]
[Lee Young sighs]
[Jaehwi’s response]
(Jeongmin) Ah, so I mean
(Nanjing) Hello
(Jaehwi) Uh, we...
Uh...
(Jeongmin) Teacher Namkyung Pyo
- Where are you going?
- The emergency room.
I want to see a patient with the intern.
(Jaehwi) Ah, my wife and I are going
Our intern...
- (Jeongmin) Teacher Tak Gion
- (Jaehwi) Ah
- (Jeongmin) Right?
- yes
(Jeongmin) Go see
(Nanjing) Goodbye
(Jeongmin) Oh, that’s right
When I heard it, interns working in obstetrics and gynecology
I heard you like Pyo Nam-kyung so much?
Me?
[lively music]
(Jeongmin) Who in particular is it and why?
You know,
(Jaehwi) Who?
I don't know, do I?
Intern who joined our department in April
(Jeongmin) Teacher Namkyung Pyo is so kind.
They teach me well and kindly
I heard you did that?
[Nankyung’s shy breathing]
Oh, I didn't do anything?
Great, next year
What if I don’t have an obstetrician/gynecologist volunteer?
I was worried, but we
(Jaehwi) All you have to do is trust Mr. Pyo Nam-kyung.
Me?
(Jaehwi) No, when deciding on a course
There are many interns who come to see the above annual leave.
Ah
(Jeongmin) And if you don’t have the annual leave below,
The ones just above you are the most difficult.
So try to persuade the interns well.
yes, i understand
Good job
yes
[Nankyung’s proud smile]
(Nanjing) Let’s go.
[Jaehwi’s light smile]
[Nankyung’s embarrassed laughter]
I hope he just seduces Tak Gion.
But are you sure that the intern is good at it?
Is that so?
Sensible and wild
(Jeongmin) It’s just the style of an obstetrician/gynecologist.
(Iksoon) Don’t worry, it’s not cholangitis.
Um, I see you're coughing too.
It's just a cold
I know someone here, don't worry
(temperature) I’m going in.
(Iksun) Yes, my brother’s teacher has come.
I'll call you back, uh
[Call end sound]
Are you Lee Ik-soon?
yes
I'll check your electrocardiogram.
Yes?
Oh, I haven't done this before?
Why are you doing it this time?
(Temperature) Uh...
I think my current symptoms are due to metastasis.
Maybe it's a heart problem
He told me to check it.
Before?
yes
If it's before...
Are you talking about cancer?
(Temperature) Uh...
Maybe recently
With a cough
Did you have severe chest tightness?
Um, cough...
yes i did
I think my chest felt a little tight too.
(Gion) Have you had major surgery before?
(Iksun) Yes, that’s right
(Gion) You must have gone through a lot back then.
Ah...
Is this very serious?
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Iksun) Wait a minute, I’m sorry.
Uh, bro not yet
Oh, don't worry
I'll call you right after I'm done
uh
[Call end sound]
[sigh]
[Calm music]
No, I barely even take the medicine anymore.
I thought it was getting better
Ha, it's really too much, really
(Chihong) Hey, what's going on?
(Iksun) Oh, are you here?
Why does it hurt so much?
[Take a deep breath]
Well, what's not to like?
(temperature) Oh, that’s it
Did you get the test results?
Can I have a CT scan?
(Temperature) Ah...
Teacher Takgion, what are you doing here?
teacher
I'm trying to get an EKG.
I think the patient was a little surprised.
[Nankyung’s puzzled groan]
Lee Ik-sun?
yes
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Nanjing) 89 years old
Lee Ik-sun?
(Temperature) 80...
[Nanjing’s sigh]
[humorous music]
Which department is it?
GS? GI?
This is obstetrics and gynecology.
[sigh]
(Nanjing) I’m really sorry, I’m sorry
Our intern
I think I got the wrong patient.
sorry
(Chihong) Checking on the patient
Isn’t it the basic of basics?
No matter how busy it is
Sounds like a mistake you should never make, right?
sorry
I will be careful
(Iksoon) Goodbye
(together) I'm sorry, I'm sorry
(Namkyung) No, that
What if I do that!
Oh, come real quick.
(temperature) I’m sorry
[Sound of curtain hitting]
[sigh]
[Iksun’s sigh]
(Iksun) Captain Ahn
The kids have lost their discipline, haven't they?
[upbeat music]
Sorry, Major Lee.
[Sniffling] I'm so surprised, I have a runny nose.
[Iksoon sniffles]
(Iksun) tissue, tissue
(Chi Hong) Tissue, tissue, tissue
(Iksun) Tissue
(Chihong) Ah, that
Are you trying to be a pigeon?
[Dove cries sound effect]
[Dove flapping wings sound effect]
I'm going to blow my nose, nose!
(Iksoon) I have a runny nose, I’m surprised
Hey, and now I
As I get older
My fingers are all stiff, I can't do a pigeon anymore
You still exercise a lot
I don't do it a lot
I'm just enduring this much by doing a lot.
[Chihong’s sigh]
What about you? Wow
It is a silhouette that does not do anything at all.
(Chi Hong) Why is my silhouette like this?
Are you completely fine? huh?
[Iksun’s sigh]
I'm a complete MZ both physically and mentally.
[sigh]
Write, oh, it's embarrassing, okay
Then, I, my older sister, will live tonight.
How MZ, what do you want to eat? pasta?
No, I saw that when I came here.
Wood-fired pizza?
Umm, I need to eat, rice.
Koreans are rice sim.
Write, in front of our hospital
Is there a really killer gomtang restaurant?
You can go there
Hey, MZ is gomtang, eat pasta
[cell phone ringing sound]
- (Iksun) MZ
- (Chihong) Teacher, wait a minute.
Yes, I'll be right there.
MZ, pasta
[Call end tone]
(Chihong) Kids these days
I like gomtang
You are already a child
Has it become a bit old?
- [Laughing] Take care of your treatment and see you later.
- (Iksun) Okay.
[Sound of curtain hitting]
(Nanjing) If it suddenly metastasized,
Who isn't surprised?
Before saying that
I should have checked one more time
sorry
Things suddenly came together
I couldn't come to my senses.
In the future, whenever I see a patient, I will definitely
Verify the patient's name and age
Check patient ID
Okay?
yes sorry
Umm, really, what is it?
Thank you though
(Gion) Another first-year teacher
You were always angry
Just tell me to fuck off
Who did that?
This is teacher Oh I-young.
Ah
But what did the teacher do wrong?
Please tell me how to do it.
I love it so much
[Calm music]
[Nanjing’s embarrassed laughter]
No matter how angry you are, it's not okay to talk rudely.
Wow, I'm not good with words.
No matter how much seniority you have, you must respect it.
[telephone ringing sound]
(Nurse 1) Yes
This is the emergency room at Jongro Yulje Hospital.
We are in full bed now
- I think you should look into other hospitals first.
- (Guardian 1) Here.
Do you know how long we've been waiting?
(Nurse 2) Yes, sorry.
I'll see you soon
(Guardian 1) When are you going to watch it, really!
(Residence in Japan) Ah, to solve the problem of cooperative patients.
I came to the emergency room briefly.
Yes, I'll be right there
[Call end sound]
Hello!
CT scan of a patient with abdominal pain
I came because you called me to say there was a problem.
(Junseok) Go to the E over there.
(Japan) Yes
(Japan) Uh, according to the CT
The ovarian cyst appears to be 3cm long.
(Patient 1) Yes, that was there originally.
But at this size
I don’t often get stomachaches?
Wait a minute
(Jae-il) Are you sick?
No, it doesn't hurt there.
Isn't the painful area downwards?
[Patient 1’s heavy sigh]
If it were because of water, wouldn't it hurt here?
So what about here?
[Patient 1’s painful elasticity]
teacher, smart
Oh, I'm busy.
(Japan) Hey teacher, I saw the patient.
The location of the pain is also different.
They say my upper stomach hurts and I can't digest it.
Ugh, why are you calling us?
(Junseok) No matter where I click
They all said it hurts.
The female patient's abdominal pain
Not all of them are obstetricians and gynecologists.
CT scan is ambiguous for cholecystitis.
Maybe Obarian Cist Torsion?
I thought it was because of this, so I called an obstetrician and gynecologist.
(Junseok) Of course, I also called a gastroenterologist.
Well, at least 3cm
It is rare for torsion to occur.
Well, it's like that
If you're worried about something, it's better to come and take a look.
Even though it was bad last week
Call an obstetrician and gynecologist
Yes, he is
Because you have a history of ovarian surgery
Last week, I had gastritis and asked him to come.
(Junseok) He is
You say you have severe menstrual cramps.
Just give me some painkillers, but I don’t need to
[hits keyboard hard]
(Junseok) Oh, when do you want me to call you quickly?
yes?
[sigh]
Obstetrics and gynecology patients in the emergency room last week
I put it on and say something about calling late.
(Junseok) Last week
Without any knowledge of obstetrics and gynecology
What diagnosis are you making?
They told me to call quickly and not waste time?
I didn't mean it that way
(Residence in Japan) These days, especially often
It's not our department, but I got a call.
So why not call?
[Makes a yuck sound]
Really?
no
[light music]
Look at that
I'll call you again when I have a patient.
(Junseok) Good luck
[sigh]
Are you a pediatrician, Moo-gang Park?
This is Sabi Kim, an obstetrician and gynecologist.
(Safety) This is Yoo Hong-seon’s mother.
Is the baby coming? Shall we go now?
No, because progress is slow.
I think the baby will come tomorrow
Oh, really?
Can I go get some food then?
yes? Am I really going to eat?
I think you can handle that yourself.
I will report on the progress of labor tomorrow morning.
I'll call you back
(Mugang) Yes
[Call end sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound effect of clock hands moving]
[Hongseon’s scream]
[Sound of door opening]
[Light music-continued]
(Sabi) Teacher, mother Hongseon Yoo
Baby is coming, please come quickly
(Mugang) Yes? Are you saying you won't come out today?
I think it will come out right away
Baby, tone down, quickly!
(Mu-gang) Oh, I want you to eat, Mr.
Let's go!
[Sound of crashing]
[Mu-gang groans in pain]
[In pain] Ah, the mountains, really, ah
[ECG meter beeping sound]
[Newborn baby cries]
[Soft music]
[Mugang’s soothing sounds for a newborn]
(Sabi) Teacher, is the baby okay?
Are you breathing well?
Yes, I heard the baby's tone is dropping.
It's nothing, I'm completely fine.
teacher
The baby is fine, why are you upset?
(Sabi) Isn’t it okay?
Why are you angry?
No, I'm not angry...
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, this is Moogang Park, a pediatrician.
(Mu-gang) Oh, it’s the baby of Park Sol’s mother in the NICU, right?
I'll be there quickly, sorry.
[Call end sound]
(Dongho) No, anesthesiology in one day
How many times are you calling it?
[Mother 5’s pained moans]
(Dongho) When applying local anesthesia
A thick needle will go in.
It may be a bit uncomfortable when the needle goes in.
yes
[Mother 5’s pained moans]
[Moaning in pain]
Have you heard of pain-free heaven?
Opening soon, please be patient.
[light music]
(Dongho) After anesthesia
It won't hurt much
relax
[Dongho’s sigh]
Anyway, once every 30 minutes
Isn't it a bit too much to call?
Do it all at once
I've been to the labor room 5 times today.
sorry
(Dongho) It’s not a lie
Now, liver transplant, cerebral hemorrhage, and peritonitis.
Three emergency surgery rooms were opened at once.
There was chaos in every operating room.
Us too
(Lee Young) Mothers take care every 30 minutes.
It hurts
Screaming at me to leave the delivery room
Husbands complain
It was very uproar
Oh, that's an obstetric situation.
The anesthesiology department is not a 5-minute standby department.
[Mother 5’s screams]
(Guardian 2) Hey, hey, teacher!
[Dongho’s sigh]
[Sound of door opening]
[Mother 5’s pained moans]
(Lee Young) Teacher!
Ah, teacher
I am a mother who was relieved of pain an hour ago.
It doesn't work
Painless again, quickly.
[Dongho’s sigh]
I...
Please keep the cancer thing a secret.
(Mutual) Speaking of my mom’s cancer
I will never have surgery
But now
What the patient also knows
Might be better for treatment
Oh, that's...
From friends to aunts this year
Everyone was suffering from cancer
Because he passed away
(Mutual) After that
If you have cancer, surgery is useless.
They say they don’t suffer in the hospital for no reason.
Because you always said that.
[sigh]
This time too
It's a lump
I barely, barely managed to trick you and bring you here.
This is the only way to do surgery
Oh, I will take responsibility after the surgery.
I'll tell you everything
[Calm music]
(Jaehwi) Grandmother of Nokdujeon in Pyeongnam Market
(Namkyung) Yes?
(Jaehwi) Just now, don’t you know?
Money is not for old people like you.
It should be used for children who will live for a long time in the future.
Every year in the pediatric department of our hospital
You donate 100 million won each.
Did you appear on You Quiz too?
(Nanjing) Ah
So, the hospital director earlier said
You came to say hello.
(Jaehwi) Yes, yes, yes
He is a person who does a lot of good things.
[Jaehwi takes a deep breath]
Wait a minute, wait a minute, um...
I think it's a small reward for that.
Let's all wear it together
Let's be careful
Well, it might be a bit of a hassle, but
(Nanjing, Gion) Yes
Everyone is home from work now, right?
If it's okay, we'll have dinner together...
- (Namkyung) I have a promise...
- (Gion) Okay, professor.
[Embarrassed laughter]
It's okay, it's okay
(Jaehwi) Why are you like this? Take it easy, take it easy
[light laughter]
yes
Let's go
Enjoy your dinner
(Namkyung) Ah, ah, ah, yes
[Jaehwi’s light smile]
Professor, enjoy your meal too.
(Jaehwi) Yes
(Dowon) Raw back ribs
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
Seasoned ribs
Whole pork belly!
eat a lot
Everyone catches me when I’m not on duty.
I really had a hard time
(Together) Let’s eat well!
(Japan) Teacher
Emergency Medicine
Are you close with teacher Park Jun-seok?
Just what
(Jae-il) Can you say something?
Because of that real emergency medicine department.
I think I'm going to lose hair due to stress.
no
When a female patient says she has a stomachache
I call the gynecologist without even looking at it properly.
Why are you calling us if you have cholecystitis?
(Dowon) Is there something you want me to see?
(Jae-il) Mmm!
That's not it, we called.
Anyone, please come quickly and take the patient.
Ugh, so people
They make fun of me because it’s a call center
Please scold the pediatrician too.
Why am I scolding them?
[Bright Music - Continued]
If I call you quickly, you’ll pout and say I called you early.
(Sabi) If you call me late
He complained that I called him late
Even things like this make me very angry.
I think it’s a pediatrician.
Because I’m very micro inside.
There are many kids like that.
There can't be many.
There is no one in the pediatrics department.
(Lee Young) Hey, what is the anesthesiology department like?
There are so many people at my bedside.
I know you're the boss
Coach driver is no joke
No, the operating room is Centipede's?
(Dowon) What about obstetrics and gynecology?
I always push my way into the operating room with a stage gun.
Threaten me with a baby and tell me to come and go
So everyone looks at us
They make fun of me and call me a gangster.
They really hate us too
And anyway, they
You don't have to ask us anything
Even if we fight, only we who always ask for it will lose.
So, get along well, get along well.
[Jaeil’s sigh]
Let’s eat today
Don't talk about the hospital while eating.
(together) yes
(Jae-il) Ah, I’m full.
Wow, I'm full.
We ate well (together)
(Lee Young) I ate well.
- (Dowon) See you tomorrow
- (Japan) Please go in.
(Namkyung) See you tomorrow!
- (Japan) Please enter carefully.
- (Sabi) Let’s go.
(Japan) Go
(Nanjing)
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Lee Young) Huh?
Weren’t you going to the hospital again?
(Dowon) No, are you going to go home?
(Lee Young) But why did you go there?
(Dowon) Yes?
[lively music]
Ah! I...
I thought the house was over there
(Lee Young) Ah
Do you think the kids will misunderstand it?
I guess it's just that the houses are facing the same direction.
They don't care about others as much as you think.
[Dowon snorts]
(Dowon) What I told you to never say
Who is it?
(Lee Young) Is that so?
(Dowon) But leave the main road behind
Why do you go to places like this?
(Lee Young) It’s the fastest way to go here.
(Dowon) It’s so dark in here
Not many people go around at night
I think it would be a bit dangerous to go alone, right?
no
And if you meet a strange person
What are you trying to do?
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
Let's throw a bamboo stick
(Lee Young) I also throw away my earplugs
[bursts of laughter]
He's a gangster
Well, in high school
Did you just do something like boxing?
(Lee Young) What do you mean?
(Dowon) There is a rumor that he is good at playing.
[Lee Young’s absurd laughter]
(Lee Young) What do you say?
[Interesting music]
[Monk’s sigh]
[Jooyoung’s satisfied moans]
[Seungwon’s happy laughter]
(Seungwon) Is it that delicious?
(Jooyoung) Yes
I think this restaurant is really the best for crab.
I'll buy more next time
I left too late
There were only two left
(Jooyoung) Hmm
I want to take care of myself
Last time I collected eggs, I saw
My stamina is so low.
I even catch a cold when I get the shot.
It was so hard
This time, I ate well and improved my condition again.
You said last time was the last time?
Are you saying you're not doing it anymore?
When did I?
See how many embryos grow
I said it would only end there.
(Jooyoung) The reason there is not a single embryo is
It wasn't in the script.
It’s invalid, it’s invalid.
Ah, after crying like that
Me? when?
I didn't cry?
[Seungwon’s light sigh]
(Jooyoung) [Satisfied] Write...
I think it'll work out this time
I got the feeling right
[Door lock button sound]
[Sound of door opening]
Huh? Why is he here already?
Put it away! Put it away, put it away
The crab ghost has come, hurry, hurry
(Lee Young) I went
- (Dowon) I went there.
- (Jooyoung) You two are coming together?
(Dowon) Yes, we had dinner together.
Ah! Not just the two of us
With all the first-year kids
(Seungwon) Haha, who said what?
(Jooyoung) Except us
I wonder if I ate something delicious
I ate ribs
I'll wash first
- (Jooyoung) Yes
- (Seungwon) Yes
But sister
[nervous music]
(Lee Young) What is this?
what?
What is this side dish?
[ding sound effect]
[Seungwon’s awkward laughter]
(Jooyoung) Huh?
[light music]
[Seungwon’s awkward laughter]
Ah!
Oh, it's Kim.
As long as I have this, what can I do?
Eat all the food, okay?
[Seungwon’s awkward laughter]
eat well
Brother-in-law, wake me up when you leave tomorrow.
(Seungwon) Okay, sister-in-law, come on.
[Sound of door opening]
Uh, what is it?
[Jooyoung and Seungwon’s light laughter]
It didn't catch me
[Sound of door closing]
[Seungwon’s laughter]
[Sound of crab being sucked]
[Lee Young’s satisfied breathing]
[Creepy sound effect]
[Tense sound effect]
[Sigh of relief]
[Sound of crab being sucked]
How did you know there was crab sauce?
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Interesting music]
(Lee Young) Did you see the soy sauce that fell next to the seaweed?
It is lighter in color than brewed soy sauce.
It has a better scent than soy sauce.
[Lee Young’s sniffing sound]
So what? It's a crab shop
[Do-won’s light smile]
This is what my brother bought for his sister-in-law.
(Do-won) At my sister-in-law’s favorite house
I would have waited in line to buy it.
So you only eat the legs.
[light laughter]
It would be better not to eat that than to eat that.
I'm still full so it tastes good
I'm just tasting it.
[Sound of crab being sucked]
But why aren't you sleeping?
I have a paper to read.
How many of those boring things are you watching?
You read the paper yesterday and the day before.
I don't even sleep
I slept every now and then at the medical office.
[Clicking tongue]
[Sound of crab being sucked]
Nothing will come out
Stop eating, I’ll buy it for you next time.
Really?
Except my sister and me
I understand
[cute music]
When?
How about this Friday?
- (Dowon) That’s right.
- (Lee Young) Wow
- (Dowon) No.
- (Lee Young) Ah!
Oh, why?
(Dowon) I have somewhere to go, but I forgot.
(Lee Young), tsk!
[Mouse operation sound]
[Keyboard operation sound]
(Jeongmin) Teacher Goo Do-won, are you on vacation starting tomorrow?
Did you pay for 3 days?
Yes, professor
(Jeongmin) Write a few more days
There's been a lot of work in the past.
I had a hard time with my thesis.
Yes? what?
Take a good rest
'Cause I won't let anyone call
(Dowon) Yes, thank you
[Sound of urgent breathing]
(Kiseon) Dowon, are you on vacation starting tomorrow?
- Is it true?
- Yes, Professor.
(Kiseon) Then, let me go today
Can’t I help out a lot and go?
It's okay, professor.
(Kiseon) Then, I will hold a summer symposium.
Presentation materials and thesis materials
Professor Lim Dong-ju’s retirement ceremony preparation plan
It would be nice if you could take a look
[Sigh of the steamer]
I can't believe what kids do
(Dowon) Yes, I understand.
(steamer) and
I have two surgeries today.
Oh, I'm going to go into all of that.
[Happy laughter]
When I'm on vacation, never, never
I won't call you, uh
-Thank you
- (Dowon) Yes
(Lee Young) I’m asking you to go on vacation or not.
[Mouse operation sound]
[Interesting music]
There was a rumor that the Chief was going on vacation.
(Dowon) Yes, professor.
Uh, are you busy today?
No, I'm not busy
(Junmo) Right?
(Dowon) Yes
Because of the surgery record
Did you get scolded a lot by Professor Jo Jun-mo?
(Nanjing) Yes
Oh my, look
(Dowon) If the surgery record shows positive
Be sure to write down the weight of your uterus
[Keyboard operation sound]
And when I draw pictures of the surgery
An arrow indicates the direction in which the uterus was taken out.
Ah!
[Mouse operation sound]
(Dowon) Yes
Ah, the first case of surgery tomorrow
To the professor tonight
I'll give you one more notice
Especially the last surgery tomorrow.
Because I have to send Frozen
Don't forget to make an appointment at the pathology department.
yes, i understand
(Namkyung) Are you coming in for surgery tomorrow?
(Dowon) Uhm, I’m not there tomorrow, I’m going on vacation.
That's right!
Oh, where are you going on vacation?
Taiwan, on a plane
(Dowon) What’s wrong with this agreement?
(Namkyung) Oh, that?
That's for grandma's pancakes.
I chose it in large letters.
Pyeongnam mung bean pancake grandmother?
The font size on the surgery consent form was too small.
I think it will be difficult to see
(Dowon) Oh
The guardian asked me to keep it a secret.
You don't know you have cancer.
Well, I wonder if it says cancer on it.
Just to check
(Dowon) Oh!
Oh, well, I have nothing to say.
(Namkyung) I’m worried about the intern.
He's a bit of a troublemaker.
You're Teacher Tak Gion, right?
Are you doing well?
(Namkyung) Um...
I am teaching well.
Boy, he trusted and relied on me a lot.
[Nanjing’s laughter]
(Dowon) Oh, oh!
(Main role) Teacher Nam-kyung Pyo
(Namkyung) Yes?
I think you should go see it.
(Namkyung) Ah...
[light music]
[Embarrassed laughter]
Wait a minute
(Patient 2) Yes
(Nanjing) Wait a minute
[Nanjing’s sigh]
Teacher Tak Gion?
It's not like putting a star on a ship.
What if I put it like that?
yes?
Ah, then how?
Long from top to bottom of the affected area
This must be placed vertically
Won't the open skin stick together well?
(Temperature) Ah...
sorry
Whenever I take a shower at home,
I'm afraid it might get in the water
(Nanjing) No
Now with Hemobag
They're not good at removing PICCs, so I do it all.
[Nankyung’s light breathing]
I just keep having more work to do.
You should be good at taping yourself.
sorry
Take care...
Please take care of me
[Nankyung’s awkward laughter]
yes
- (Nanjing) Patient
- (Patient 2) Yes
(Namkyung) I guess the tape
I think I'll have to take it off and put it back on.
(Patient 2) Do this again?
(Namkyung) Ah, yes
Avoid getting water in the shower
Be careful
When you come to the next outpatient visit
Check whether the wound has healed well
I'll dress you again.
yes
(Jaehwi) Hello
I heard you're going down early tomorrow morning by car.
I rushed to prepare for discharge.
(Patient 2) Thank you
Oh, by the way, professor.
Is this okay?
(Patient 2) Isn’t it going to fall soon?
I want to have it
(Namkyung) Oh, you don’t have to worry.
I put it on well
No, the male teacher over there earlier was
You attached it very carefully.
(Patient 2) What the teacher added here is a little bit
I'm anxious
(Jaehwi) Well, if I do that
I'll take a look again
Um, did you attach it well?
(Patient 2) Oh, really?
(Jaehwi) Sseu-eup
Isn't it amazing?
[Proud laughter]
No, our male teacher
How did you put it on?
Are you saying it was put together better than this?
[humorous music]
(Patient 2) Oh, make sure not a single drop of water gets in.
How carefully did you paste it?
I put it back on for no reason
Oh no, that's not it...
(Jaehwi) Oh, it’s okay, it’s okay.
Ah, in times like this, put some humility in your mind.
(temperature) Yes?
Ah...
(Jaehwi) Oh
(Gion) Ah... thank you
(Jaehwi) Miss, I’m curious.
[Awkward laughter]
[Announcement sound]
- (Sabi) Oh Iyoung, what are you doing?
- (Lee Young) Oh, it’s a surprise.
I'm trying to get money
What about you?
- I had some savings.
- Savings?
(Sabi) Uh, it’s expired so I’m canceling it.
Expiration?
Wow, there's someone who can do that.
(Sabi) You may suddenly need a lot of money.
You can move
I can go on a trip, I have to save up.
You don't do it because you don't know, or you don't do it because you can't do it.
Don’t you have savings?
Have you never tried it before?
Wow, there are people who live like that.
[ATM operating sound]
But I do do something similar.
What are you doing?
Lotto, there is a good place in front of my house
They say he came in first place 8 times.
[light sigh]
[cell phone ringing sound]
(together) Huh?
I guess the mother has arrived
- (Lee Young) Yes, teacher.
- (Sabi) Yes
(Lee Young) Ah, yes, I’ll go right away.
- (Sabi) I'm on my way, teacher.
- (Lee Young) No, no, no
[Sound of newborn babies crying]
(Sabi) 10cm to the left
I think 5cm to the right should be enough?
(Mugang) Hey, teacher.
What kind of parking lot is this?
(Sabi) Just push a little bit
Just one size fits all
I think it will work
I have no one to take care of
Can it be solved by just pushing Bassinet?
'Cause you can't push the baby in
I need to push this in.
(Mugang) We’re still saturated.
Yesterday, there were three mothers with twins.
Don't you remember?
I remember
2 o'clock, 5 o'clock, 1 a.m.
(Mugang) Oh, right?
Obstetrics and delivery are three.
Our pediatrics department is growing by six, you know?
It's not because we don't want to receive it.
Oh, it really doesn't work...
[Newborn baby cries]
[Mugang’s soothing sounds for a newborn]
Are you hungry?
Wait a minute
Baby, you're pretty
There is no one
Don’t you even watch the news?
Our pediatric department has no applicants.
Not even a year
One by one, everyone disappears.
So I'm on duty, on duty, on duty
I've barely slept for 36 hours now.
I think that's a pity too.
But why do you always ask me
Are you talking about the reality of pediatrics?
[sigh]
I'm telling you it can't be done.
[Laughing awkwardly] No.
(Sabi) I can’t either.
Professor Seo Jeong-min
All the mothers said they couldn't go.
No, then when the baby is born
Will the teacher give me food?
I gave him food, held him, and slept with him...
[Embarrassed laughter]
Are you going to hug me and put me to sleep?
Can I hold you and feed you?
(Sabi) If I give you food
Can I put a bassinet in it?
Hey there
[cell phone ringing sound]
Yes, this is Moogang Park, a pediatrician.
(Mu-gang) Is Heeyul throwing up? I'll be right there
[Call end sound]
Oh, I clearly said no.
Just add a bassinet, really.
[Splendid music]
[Call connection tone]
(Sabi) Lee Young-ah, you’re settled in.
(Lee Young) Okay
Oh!
- (Dongho) There is no room.
- (Lee Young) There’s no room, right?
I know, I have to, it’s urgent.
(Dongho) It must be urgent.
To open the room now
Another surgery needs to be delayed.
No, I had obstetrics yesterday early in the morning too.
All other surgeries were postponed
How much we were criticized
(Lee Young) Please, just this once.
Do we really have to have a C-section?
(Dongho) You saw it on the way here.
Right now, there are no anesthesiologists and no room.
The surgery itself is impossible.
(Lee Young) Then it will never happen.
Is that what you mean?
(Dongho) Yes
(Lee Young) Then, to the mother,
Because I can't do surgery because of the anesthesiology department.
I'll tell everyone to go.
[lively music]
(Dongho) Huh, what?
No, are you threatening me now?
(Lee Young) Otherwise
Until the anesthesiologist gives me a room
Just hold on to having a baby
Shall I tell you?
(Dongho) Wow, that was really bad, that was really bad.
(Lee Young) I am now
Because it’s not the time to look after someone’s situation.
They say there is no hospital that will accept me right now.
[Dongho’s sigh]
[Call connection tone]
(Dongho) Uh, Sanghyun.
Just postpone the decision to have that OS surgery for a little while.
Oh, just wish you one more time
It's not an emergency there.
uh
Just one hour
Who could it be, Sanggwaji?
[Soft music]
(Lee Young) Thank you!
[Call connection tone]
(Lee Young) Ah, professor, we have set up the operating room.
I'm going to give birth.
[Noisy noise]
(Japan) Teacher
I got a call saying the mother was here.
(Junseok) Stay over there, I’ll be right there.
(Japan) Yes
[Patient 3 groans in pain]
- (Junseok) Call the neurosurgeon.
- (Resident 1) Yes
I'll disinfect it, it stings.
(Jaeil) Ah, I have quite a fever.
teacher
Did you get the maternal CBC and CRP results?
(Junseok) Ah
Ha, I haven't done that yet.
What about UA?
I was going to do that too
Because the mother says she can't urinate
I haven't done it yet
Ah...
So you're calling me when the test hasn't even been done?
[Awkward laughter]
[shameful breathing]
I'm sorry, Teacher Eom Jae-il.
Maybe a maternal test
Can you please take me up to the delivery room and do some work for me?
(Junseok) When we are busy
Other obstetricians and gynecologists
They said they would do that.
There are a lot of patients today
It's a full bed now
Hey, look here.
(Japan) Ah!
It's the same as our delivery room.
[lively music]
[sigh]
The labor room is now full beds.
It's real chaos.
(Junseok) Oh, I see.
[Junseok’s sigh]
But why not just once?
(Japan) Write...
Ah...
Is this going to happen?
sorry
We are too busy
[Soft music]
(Jaeil) Please take a urine test.
Blood tests: CBC, CRP, PCT
Electro, OTPT, BUN
Give me creatinine
If you can inspect Apé Sono as well,
I quickly and accurately
I'll upload it to the mother.
[Junseok’s helpless groan]
yes
Then, please contact me when you finish the inspection.
thank you
(Resident 1) You’ve become a lot smarter, haven’t you?
(Junseok) Ha, it was a failure.
Ah, it wasn't that kind of character originally.
- Teacher, I'm going to take a blood test here.
- (Nurse 3) Yes
(Together) It looks delicious.
(Lee Young) Wow, nice, nice, nice
(Nanjing) Let’s eat, let’s eat, let’s eat, let’s eat
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
- (Jaeil) Enjoy your meal!
- (Namkyung, Lee Young) Enjoy your meal!
[Lee Young’s satisfied moans]
I didn't even have the strength to break the bones, but the boneless meat was a mess.
The mother said she was my lord.
Thanks to you, I don’t have to go to another hospital.
I had a good baby
[Jaeil’s satisfying elasticity]
(Jaeil) That’s right, chicken on a good day
(Namkyung) Hey, but you guys
Why do you feel so good, huh?
at 11:30
I can't even go home right now and I'm like this.
(Japan) I got a kick out of the emergency medicine department.
Hitting the bone with a fact
You said it was made with boneless meat?
Hey, good job
Because everyone tolerates us
I think you're really stupid
(Japan) That’s right
What blessings are there if you endure it?
I got a vase
No!
Don't hold back y'all, eh? be careful!
That's right, if you can endure it three times
I held back too much
no more
(Nanjing) What, what is it?
Why are you three suddenly like this?
Can you communicate well?
Now, what a single mind! Daedong unity!
What are you doing like this?
Is that right?
[Knocking sound]
(Dowon) Guys
Take care of maternal operability after surgery
MFICU mother Hojin Ahn
Because it looks like I'm going to give birth soon
I need to watch carefully to see if the contractions are going well.
(together) yes
(Jae-il) But haven’t you gotten off work yet?
Isn't there a flight tomorrow morning?
I'm just going to pack my bags and go, bye bye.
(Dowon) Ah, ah!
You guys called and said, where are you?
Excuse me, can I ask one question?
You especially Eom Jae-il
Don't do that, I won't let you.
Ah!
The vacation isn't 3 months, it's only 3 days?
What do you think of us?
(Namkyung) We’re doing it now too, right?
Don't worry
(Sabi) Have a nice trip
The gift just needs to be small.
yes
see you next week
- (Japan) Please be careful.
- (Nanjing) Take care.
(Xavi) If you ask a question, ask the Chief.
(Jaeil) I was wrong
It's the chief's fault for not checking.
Bring it to me quickly
(Lee Young) How many times do I tell you that I don’t have a rescuer?
[Sound of hitting the wall]
The shocking thing is
I haven't even been on vacation for a day yet
[Everyone sighs]
[Mobile phone call incoming sound]
(Namkyung) Huh?
[Nanjing’s sigh]
Everyone is looking for Mr. Chief.
Why is he only looking for me?
- (Japan) Who?
- (Nanjing) Intern
I feel anxious when left alone and angry when we are together.
Gu Do-won must have been like that too, right?
[Everyone sighs]
(Nanjing) I have to go before something happens.
[lively music]
Going
[Everyone sighs]
[Sigh of temperature]
(temperature) Ah, this is different from that.
Consent form for painless injection
When you're sick
I'm going to use medicine that won't hurt.
What is it about?
If you look here
(Jaok) No, I just removed a small lump.
That must be really painful?
[Mutual clears cough]
It's different for each person.
Because you are older
Because it might hurt a little more
We want to prepare medicine in advance.
How long does it take to remove the lump?
Yes, if you do all the preparation and anesthesia,
About an hour and a half
(Jaok) Hmm
It's taking longer than I thought
Yes, cancer surgery usually takes a while.
(temperature) Still, compared to other cancer surgeries,
It's short
(Jaok) Yes, really?
Cancer surgery?
yes
Who?
I?
[heavy music]
If I have cancer surgery, it means I have cancer.
Ho, it’s not a lump, it’s cancer?
Yes, I...
It's cancer...
(Jaok) So
From a long time ago, I was the only one left out
Everyone knew, did I have cancer?
Everyone in the hospital together
How do you fool a patient?
(Mutual) I asked for it, I
Mom, it was obvious that you wouldn’t want to have surgery.
(Jaehwi) Are you having surgery?
In the video, it looks like the very beginning.
And it is expected that the progress will be good.
And this laparoscopic surgery
The wound is not big
So recovery will be quick.
I thought my brother would be able to survive too.
In the end, I ended up having a hard time at the hospital.
Oh no, I won't waste my time like that.
Because we're all old now
Are you asking me to stop living?
Is it okay to just die when you get old?
(Mutual) Huh?
Who says that?
Oh, it's in the law, it's in the books?
Let's do the surgery, Mom, okay?
Cook more pancakes
Let’s get more kids operated on.
I'm not asking you to live with your mother.
Let's save the kids, kids.
Do you hate that too?
uh?
mom
(Jaehwi) Your son is right.
(Nanjing) Have surgery, patient.
Please, really.
(temperature) I was wrong
I'm sorry, grandma, please
[sigh]
I had no intention of having surgery.
I feel bad that everyone fooled me.
I was going to go home right away
(Jaok) Because of the teacher here
I'll think again
Because I’m thankful
Ah, but that's really not a big deal.
For telling me honestly
[light music]
(Jaok) If it weren’t for the teacher
What kind of disease am I?
I don't even know what happens to my body
I almost got taken to the operating room.
Where in the world is such an idiot?
Thanks for talking to me.
The only person I can trust is my teacher.
I'm an old man who doesn't know anything
Would it have been easy to deceive?
(Namkyung) No...
(Jaehwi) I’m sorry
(Nanjing) I’m sorry
If you have surgery
Is the teacher coming too?
Yes, I will definitely go, Grandma.
[Embarrassed laughter]
(Jaehwi) Write...
Yes, then
(Mutual) Yes, over there, but
This is the consent form for surgery.
Ah, but why is the writing like this?
(Namkyung) Oh, it’s easier for you to see grandma.
I made the font bigger and selected it in advance.
Oh, I heard you’ve read it?
- My mother can’t read Korean.
- (Namkyung) Yes?
[humorous music]
(Mutual) I think I told you that once.
He just left it behind
(Namkyung) Ah...
(Mutual) I...
All I have to do is get mom's signature here, right?
Ah, that
No, I gave it to you so you can see it in advance.
When receiving your signature, please read it again carefully.
(Jaehwi) Let me explain.
(Mutual) Ah, yes, thank you.
[light sigh]
(Gion) Yes, I eat at home too.
(Ja-ok) Oh, my goodness
[Gion’s laughter]
(Namkyung) You’re going to be a bastard
[Keyboard operation sound]
You can just do anything that works
No matter what I do, it works out well
Ah, the timing
It can't be just like that, huh?
[happy laughter]
[Interesting music]
Hey, when you're on duty
There aren't any calls
Huh? In my case, it took all night.
Oh, if you're going to get annoyed, just go home.
If you're not going, you can stand on duty instead of me.
(Namkyung) Ha, because of emergency surgery.
Professor Jaehwi Ryu’s two surgeries were delayed.
I can't go now!
Those who can't do it must be really tired.
This is Mr.
[happy laughter]
Oh, Mr. Hwak!
[light sigh]
[Sound of door opening]
(Jeongmin) I, Jin Jin-hyo, am going into labor.
I'm doing a good job checking the ward and emergency room.
yes
[telephone ringing sound]
Yes, this is an obstetrics and gynecology department.
Oh, yes, I'll be right there.
[Sound of putting down receiver]
(Junseok) Not a mother at our hospital.
My water has already broken.
[Ultrasound machine operating sound]
maternal body
Your Amniotic Membrane Ruptured
So, water break, you no?
[Lee Young’s embarrassed exclamation]
What’s Your Name?
[Russian]
[Korean] What do you mean?
Name, name, name
name
Margarita Kalashnikova
- Margarita?
- (Margarita) Margarita
Margarita?
Two, two, two
(Lee Young) Two? Twin?
Twins?
Isn't it? There was one?
They're twins
Second, the first was a caesarean section and now the second.
(Lee Young) Ah!
Ah, understand, second baby
Okay, okay
subashiba
[dark music]
Professor, in the emergency room.
A mother who needs surgery has arrived.
She is not a mother at our hospital, but she is a ROM.
(Lee Young) According to the ultrasound, it is a baby bridge.
There is an active raver
Felvik Award is 1.5 and 50
I think I need to go into surgery.
I called you in advance
(Jeongmin) Uh, I’m in labor, it’ll be over soon.
I'm preparing for surgery, I'll finish it and leave.
(Lee Young) Yes
[Call end sound]
(Jeongmin) Wait a minute
Wow, you're bleeding heavily?
(Jaehwi) Well, our intern teacher is
I keep my promise to my grandmother.
How long are you standing up this night?
(temperature) is okay
(Jaehwi) He’s kind to the patients.
I get a lot of praise for doing a good job.
I heard everyone only talks about our teacher Tak Gion.
(Barley) Huh? Did you memorize the professor’s name?
(Jaehwi) [surprised] Huh?
Ah, yes
I engraved it in my heart.
[Nankyung’s awkward laughter]
[The sound of the wind blowing in Nanjing]
(Jaehwi) During my internship
That's what it means to be told you're good at something
It's not easy
That's right, we...
(Nanjing) Yes?
Yes, that's right, that's right, that's right
(Gion) Thank you
(Jaehwi) Anyway, we will continue in the future
I wish I had seen you for a long time
Should I fan myself a little?
(Namkyung) Yes?
(Jaehwi) Fanning
(Namkyung) Ah, yes
I was just like this
I'm not the type to sweat a lot.
Wow, it’s unusually hot today
(Jaehwi) Ah...
Uh, wait a minute
Uh, there, the wound here, not there.
You put glue on the wound here.
(Namkyung) Ah! Oh, here, here?
Oh, here?
(Jaehwi) Oh, wait a minute
- Give me a moment.
- (Nanjing) Here...
[lively music]
[Jaehwi’s laughter]
(Jaehwi) No, the teacher in our major is like this.
Was he this funny?
[Nankyung’s embarrassed laughter]
Huh? Oh, look at this
Look at this, look at this, mountain, obstetrics and gynecology
It's so much fun, isn't it?
(Gion) Yes, it’s so funny
(Jaehwi) It’s really here
It's a happy place, isn't it?
(Namkyung) Ah, yes, I’m happy.
[Jaehwi’s laughter]
(Jaehwi) Oh, why are you like this?
Ah, why is it so hot today?
[Nankyung’s embarrassed laughter]
It's hot?
You worked hard
- (Nanjing) Take care.
- (Temperature) Thank you for your hard work.
[Sound of holding back laughter]
Mr. Takgion
Are you laughing?
Is this funny!
[Call connection tone]
Lady, why isn’t the anesthesiologist answering the phone?
Ah, doctor, it's obstetrics.
(Lee Young) I have to have emergency maternal surgery.
Fasting?
Fasting...
Diju dinner? Eat dinner?
[Russian]
[Korean] Check it out right away
I'll call you back
Well then, just get a room first...
[Call end sound]
Mr. Lee, tsk.
[Russian]
Diju it anything?
[Lee Young’s embarrassed sigh]
(Lee Young) Food
[Korean] Translator, translator, translator, translator
[Margarita’s painful exclamation]
Oh?
[nervous music]
Does it hurt? Does your stomach hurt? uh?
Oh, don't worry, don't worry
Mistress
Everything okay, don't worry, don't worry
don't worry
Excuse Me
Oh!
Uh, what is it?
Why is this now...
When are you uploading the post for the new mother?
- Now.
- (Junseok) Yes?
(Lee Young) Now baby’s feet, now
The baby's foot is missing, now!
- (Junseok) Here, teacher!
- (Nurse 4) Yes
(Marcarita) [Russian]
Listen, You Have to Surgery Now
Uh, uh, friend, everything is okay
Baby okay, don't worry
[Korean] Hey, the baby’s foot fell off.
I need to upload it quickly
(Junseok) Contact your guardian quickly
- Please find out the mother’s history.
- (Nurse 4) Yes
(Junseok) Oh, I’ll take the anesthesiology department.
(Lee Young) Ah, thank you!
[Call connection tone]
(Junseok) Oh, please open the operating room for me.
Ah, open it first, ah, obstetrics, obstetrics
- (Lee Young) Professor, you have to come.
- (Junseok) Oh, quickly.
(Lee Young) The baby’s foot is missing, foot!
(Jeongmin) Here and now in Bazaar or Damage
My rectum was torn and I'm in the process of receiving treatment.
Do you think it will take some time?
(Lee Young) Yes? So what should I do?
(Jeongmin) Is there anyone who can come?
[Nervous music - continued]
At least call your wife and the professor on duty.
I asked for it, quickly
[Margarita moans in pain]
Professor Jaehwi Ryu went to emergency surgery.
What should I really do?
(Jeongmin) Then, Teacher Oh Iyoung is preparing.
I'll switch hands with GS and go right away.
If you are in a hurry while preparing
I'm taking a generic and opening my stomach as soon as I'm anesthetized.
(Lee Young) Yes
Yes?
(Jeongmin) Keep it open, it’ll be gone soon
[Call end tone]
GS Please call the professor on duty.
Can Ki-seon and Myeong-won come?
- Please check.
- (Jiyoung) Yes
[Margarita's scream]
(Junseok) Do you have a room?
(Dongho) Yes, with the ladies.
All the nursing teachers came and cleaned it up.
I had to postpone one surgery later.
(Lee Young) Thank you, teacher
(Dongho) Does the mother have any underlying diseases?
-What medicine do you take?
- (Lee Young) I don’t know.
(Dongho) What about fasting?
(Lee Young) I don’t know
(Dongho) How many kilograms does the mother weigh?
Do you know my name?
(Lee Young) It’s too long, sorry.
[Margarita screams in pain]
It's okay, don't worry
I'm a Famous Doctor, Don't Worry
(Mu-gang) Isn’t this obstetrician and gynecologist Oh I-young?
(Nurse 5) I think that’s right?
(Mugang) Ah, at that speed, it seems like a pretty big deal.
Ah, what is it again!
[Margarita’s painful exclamation]
[heavy music]
(Dongho) Please tell me when you’re ready.
The anesthesia is ready.
[Lee Young’s crying]
Teacher Oh I-young, you can’t cry.
When tears fall, this is it
You have to put it back on and do it again, okay?
(Lee Young) Yes...
(Dongho) Hey, if you need to take the baby out
(Lee Young) That’s not possible.
(Dongho) I understand it’s scary, but...
(Mugang) Has the baby’s foot fallen off?
How long has it been?
(Junseok) I checked the missing foot 10 minutes ago.
Mother's name is Margarita Kalashnikova.
37th week of pregnancy, early pregnancy
I have a history of going to the emergency room at our hospital.
They said there was nothing special at that time.
My husband contacted me and he is coming.
First, verbal consent to the surgery was obtained.
uh, thank you
Please find someone who can come
(Dongho) [Russian]
Okay?
Okay
(Mugang) [Korean] I think I should open my stomach, right?
(Lee Young) I can’t do it, I haven’t tried it before.
(Mugang) On my missing leg
If the blood doesn't flow, you'll be in big trouble.
[Lee Young’s embarrassed groan]
(Junseok) I’m still looking for someone who can come.
First of all, I will take care of you too.
(No lecture) Even if the baby is exposed to anesthesia
I just need to wake you up, so take it slow.
I'll take good care of the baby, okay?
(Dongho) That’s right
I will also be taking good care of the mother.
Calm down
We're all here
[Lee Young’s scared breathing]
When teacher Oh I-young puts in a blind spell
You need to pull it down a bit.
(Junseok) Yes, I understand.
[Lee Young’s nervous sigh]
[Lee Young sighs]
[Medical device operation sound]
[dark music]
(Dongho) I was anesthetized.
vitals are ok
[Lee Young’s trembling breathing]
[Lee Young’s nervous breathing]
[Lee Young’s nervous sigh]
(Dowon) Open deeper
(Lee Young) Teacher!
[Lee Young’s crying]
[Junseok sighs in relief]
[Mugang sighs in relief]
[Calm music]
[Lee Young’s crying]
(Dowon) Come to your senses
[Lee Young’s trembling breathing]
[Dowon’s sigh]
[Dowon’s nervous breathing]
[Sound of pear slicing]
(Do-won) Anesthesiologist
(Dongho) The mother’s vitals are okay.
- (Dowon) And
- (Mugang) Oh, I also contacted the NICU.
- Don't worry
- (Dowon) Yes, thank you.
pull
(Sanghyun) Yes
Yes, it's the obstetrics and gynecology department's on-call room, but there's no one there.
Yes, please contact me again.
yes
[Call end sound]
[Closes cell phone]
What should I do? I don’t think there’s anyone there, tsk.
[Sanghyun sighs]
Oh, what should I do?
[Sanghyeon’s surprised groan]
What is it?
(Dowon) This isn’t Taiwan.
Oh, I bought a plane ticket.
[Dowon’s sigh]
[Sanghyeon’s surprised groan]
(Sanghyun) Obstetrics and gynecology
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Dowon) The baby is coming
[Lee Young’s heavy breathing]
(Yunjeong) 20:46 It’s a boy.
(Dowon) Take the baby, quickly.
(Mu-gang) Uh, please wrap the sensor.
- Please clean the baby.
- (Junseok) Yes
(Mugang) I have to cry
Baby, let's cry
Heart rate less than 100 beats
I will proceed with positive pressure ventilation.
- Let me give you some oxygen.
- (Junseok) Yes
(Jeongmin) Lee Young-ah, are you okay?
(Lee Young, Dongho) Professor!
(Jeongmin) Did you get the baby out safely?
(Lee Young) Yes
- (Professor of Anesthesiology) Are the mother’s vitals okay?
- (Dongho) Yes
(Professor of Anesthesiology) Oh, you worked hard, go get some rest.
(Dongho) Yes, professor.
(Jeongmin) Are you okay?
-Lee Young-ah, change your seat.
- (Lee Young) Yes
(Do-won) The baby was brought out and the uterus is contracting well.
(Jeongmin) Well done
[Beep sound]
(Mugang) What is your heart rate?
[heavy music]
(Junseok) Less than 100 episodes
- (No lecture) Please stimulate the baby more.
- (Junseok) Yes
(Mugang) Baby, let’s cry
[ECG meter operating sound]
[Newborn baby cries]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
[Mu-gang and Jun-seok sigh in relief]
[Lee Young and Dongho sigh in relief]
[Lee Young sighs in relief]
[Newborn baby cries]
(Jeongmin) Is the baby okay?
(No lecture) Yes, Apgar is 8 points.
Saturation is okay
The pulse is over 100 beats.
First, I will move you to the NICU.
(Jeongmin) Thank you for your hard work.
(Mugang) You worked hard too
[Newborn baby cries]
(Jeongmin) Oh Yiyoung!
Well done, really good.
(Lee Young) Thank you
(Professor of Anesthesiology) Maternal vitals are good.
Dongho also had a hard time
(Dongho) Thank you
[Dongho sighs in relief]
(Jeongmin) Oh Iyoung’s control has been completed
The two of us held hands while we were together
go out and get some rest
[Lee Young’s light sigh]
[Lee Young’s sobbing moans]
[cell phone ringing sound]
Hey, Ki-dong-dong!
(Namkyung) Huh?
Where are you now?
(Movement) Nam Kyung-ah
Ki Dong Ah
[Nanjing’s sigh]
(Chihong) Yes, professor.
The patient who contacted me
Arrived safely at the emergency room
On CT, EDH is located on the right temporal side.
The amount is quite large
Uh, it's a mental stuper and the left motor is
It's about grade 3 away.
Yes, I will upload the operating room right now.
yes
[Call end sound]
- Hello, teacher.
- (Chihong) Huh?
Obstetrics and gynecology, right?
(Nanjing) Yes, that obstetrics and gynecology department.
This is Pyo Nam-kyung, a first-year student.
It's no different in relation to patients.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Uh, yeah
(Nankyung) Uh, on the stairs
This is a patient who came in after falling.
Oh, Jo Sook-hee?
(Nanjing) Yes
I want to know the results of the test.
(Chi Hong) Oh, wait a minute.
um
Yes, according to CT
Well, there is no brain hemorrhage or skull fracture.
(Namkyung) Ah...
But I heard you fell hard.
Take it easy for about a week
If there is anything wrong
You need to come to the hospital right away.
yes, thank you
(Chihong) But isn’t this a gynecological patient?
(Namkyung) Yes?
There's no record like that on the charts?
(Namkyung) Ah, yes
That's not it
Are you my boyfriend’s mother?
Oh, I see.
- That son from earlier?
- (Nanjing) Yes
(Chihong) Oh my, the guardian
I think you were a bit surprised.
Our resident explained it well.
Teacher, please say it again.
yes, thank you
- (Resident 2) Professor
- (Chihong) Yes
(Resident 2) Patient with pallidoma
CTNGO results are out.
MCA Aneurism Rupture
- Arrange the operating room and prepare for clipping.
- (Resident 2) Yes
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
(Nanjing) CT showed no brain damage.
No bleeding
They say there's nothing wrong with my bones
(Movement) You’re not seriously injured, right?
Isn’t there something wrong with your brain?
(Namkyung) Yes, everything is okay for now.
[Sigh of relief]
Thank goodness
thank you
Thank you so much, Namkyung.
I'm glad you stopped
(Nankyung) I must have been really surprised.
(start) Yes
Are you still very angry with me?
Where else are you angry?
It's all over
(Gi-Dong) I’m sorry for messing with your contact.
When you start answering texts
Then I called
I wonder if we'll meet again then
Hey, what's wrong with the fight?
We broke up, Namkyung.
(Movement) I told you
If you decide to break up again
I will really understand then
No, I was just angry...
[Gidong makes a yuck sound]
Hey, I
I told you
In a fit of anger
I'm the type of person you can ask to break up with.
I was so sad
But I endured it
Well, because you were that good
[Sad music]
Ki-dong...
(Move) Fight with me
I knew you were going on a blind date when you weren't in contact.
I told my friends I was a job seeker.
I thought you were trying to embarrass me
I just pretended not to notice
Because I feel like I’m not enough
But this time
The day you said to break up
For the first time, I wasn't sad but relieved.
Now you, not me
I think I can hate you
But anyway
I called you again like this
Because mom collapsed
As my hair turns white, this happens
All I could think of was you
You are the only doctor I know
I shouldn’t have called though.
sorry
I won't do that again
I was thankful for today
(Namkyung) Hey, Hong Ki-dong!
call me
I hate it
Have to go to the hospital again
Well, if someone gets sick or gets hurt,
call me
(Nanjing) Hey
It's been 7 years for us
But just because we broke up, doesn’t that mean I can’t even ask for something like that?
[Sad music-continued]
Don't ask me to meet you again
I won't even ask you to be friends
So call me when you need me
You go, mom will wait for you.
Okay
I'll go first
Going
[Nankyung’s sobbing sound]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
[Crying]
What's going on?
[Nankyung’s sniffling sound]
[Gion’s laughter]
Hey
Are you laughing?
Are you finding this funny now?
sorry
[Nankyung’s Crying]
(Jeongmin) I endured it for ten years.
It's been a few years since I've been in the mountains and jjambap, but emergency
Ah, I can't get used to it.
(Dowon) Professor, what would we think?
(Jeongmin) Thank you, Goo Do-won
You guys saved the baby.
Teacher Oh I-young, are you okay?
Should I at least eat Cheongsimwon?
(Dowon) I’ll take a look.
(Jeongmin) Yes
But
[Jeongmin sighs]
Compared to what you do
Write it, do it well
Quick hands and fearless
(Dowon) That’s right.
(Jeongmin) Oh, that’s right
[Jeongmin sighs]
But why are you here?
Sleeping like someone else
It's not like I couldn't go on vacation.
Is there anyone else like that?
Me last year
[Dowon’s laughter]
[Jeongmin’s laughter]
(Jeongmin) Still
The last time I performed a bridge section
That helped, right?
Isn't that me?
Today is my first day, Professor.
Really?
Wow, Gudowon!
Has it grown a lot?
(Jeongmin) Who raised him so well?
uh? I'm not?
- (Dowon) No, no, I
- (Jeongmin) Did you grow up alone?
(Do-won) I was earlier
I almost cried when I opened the boat.
There were so many people watching, I could barely hold back.
Oh!
Are you gentler than me?
(Dowon) Oh no, no.
You didn't know?
[cell phone ringing sound]
Uh, Mr. Myeong-won.
To avoid fibroids
You can just go into J Injeon.
Why are you calling me while doing that?
Going
(Jeongmin) I’ll go now
[Call end sound]
(Dowon) Please enter.
[Mobile phone call incoming sound]
(Lee Young) Can’t you buy me coffee?
[Exciting music]
[Do-won’s light smile]
[Rain sound]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
Take one of these
(Dongho) You seemed very surprised earlier.
(Lee Young) Ah!
thank you
I had a hard time today
Ah, thank you so much
Thank you so much
yes
Yes...
(Dongho) It’s raining. Can’t I go in?
(Lee Young) Ah, yes
I decided to meet someone.
Oh, I see.
Then
(Dongho) Ah, child, I’m sorry.
Oh, I use this.
(Lee Young) No, it’s okay
I use it
You can return it later.
thank you
When returning the umbrella
Would you like to eat together then?
[Music: 'Someday I'll Be Wise'
‘Life as a Major’ OST-Continued]
‘Life as a Major’ OST]
(Lee Young) It’s hard.
What I'm smiling about these days is not smiling
More than what you see
I like it a lot more
Not riding?
(Dongho) Oh, we have some left to talk about.
(Lee Young) Hey
I have one question
(Japan) Let’s eat together
It's a date request.
- (Sabi) With who?
- (Nanjing) Looks like a man
(Jaeil) You like it?
(Jaehwi) Welcome, mother.
[Nankyung Mo’s embarrassed laughter]
(Nankyung) Mom, don’t really talk about me.
Oh, really don't do it.
(Lee Young) Wherever the dumplings are placed
Namkyung Pyo TMI is no joke
(Nankyung Mo) Hey, just eat one and go.
(Namkyung) Ah, Mom!
(Dahye) If it’s one year, come out a little early, huh?
(Eunmi) How can you not pay for your work?
(Junmo) Hey, why are you...
Hey, come here, quick! Come here!
Sabi Kim?
Hey Sabi!
(Lee Young) Are you serious?
(Nanjing) It’s not malignant cancer, right?
I...
I want to go back again